​​​ ​Take off your blindfolds!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is Alison, and if she spends ​ ​​
​​ ​thirty days​ ​​
​​​ ​chained to one of these strangers,​ ​​
​​​ ​I will give her two hundred ​ ​​
​​ ​fifty thousand dollars.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, waaaiit.​ ​​
​​​ ​But you choose which one you chain ​ ​​
​​ ​yourself to based on looks alone.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, I get to pick?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, you get to pick.​ ​​
​​​ ​That granny,​ ​​
​​​ ​this biker,​ ​​
​​​ ​or the gym bro.​ ​​
​​​ ​Choose carefully.​ ​​
​​​ ​Because the one chained ​ ​​
​​ ​to you at the end​ ​​
​​​ ​will have the chance to ​ ​​
​​ ​steal the whole prize.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, this is hard.​ ​​
​​​ ​Only having that information...​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna have to go with​ ​​
​​​ ​the middle biker.​ ​​
​​​ ​You don't even know his name.​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll have plenty of time ​ ​​
​​ ​to figure that out​ ​​
​​​ ​Two hundred fifty thousand ​ ​​
​​ ​dollar decision.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's see if it pays off.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right, here you go.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey!​ ​​
​​​ ​How you doing?​ ​​
​​​ ​Nice to meet you...​ ​​
​​​ ​Bryce.​ ​​
​​​ ​Alison.​ ​​
​​​ ​My hands are sweaty. I'm nervous.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, boooyy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahh, ha ha!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's gonna be an interesting video.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is where you'll be living. ​ ​​
​​ ​You got your kitchen.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know how to cook, but...​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you know how to cook?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm pretty good. Nah, I'm pretty good.​ ​​
​​​ ​We got your living room...​ ​​
​​​ ​Love iiiit.​ ​​
​​​ ​Any questions?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ummm​ ​​
​​​ ​How do I use the bathroom with this?​ ​​
​​​ ​Just go inside.​ ​​
​​​ ​Put it under the floor...​ ​​
​​​ ​And there you go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh-- DON'T​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't do that! Oh, no!​ ​​
​​​ ​ha hAA HAA!​ ​​
​​​ ​The only rules are:​ ​​
​​​ ​you can't step on ​ ​​
​​ ​the red line outside​ ​​
​​​ ​or take off the handcuffs.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll let these two strangers get to ​ ​​
​​ ​know each other.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, is it a bad time to say I wish I ​ ​​
​​ ​chose Granny?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah. I could be a backstabber. You ​ ​​
​​ ​have no idea.​ ​​
​​​ ​You know the gist. We have hidden ​ ​​
​​ ​cameras covering every inch of this house...​ ​​
​​​ ​...Minus the bathroom.​ ​​
​​​ ​And what Alison doesn't realize​ ​​
​​​ ​is this isn't the only stranger​ ​​
​​​ ​in this video she will be chained to.​ ​​
​​​ ​And they will all have a chance​ ​​
​​​ ​to steal the quarter of a ​ ​​
​​ ​MILLION dollars from Alison.​ ​​
​​​ ​Things are gonna get very interesting.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's see how it goes.​ ​​
​​​ ​Which bed's mine?​ ​​
​​​ ​I want that one right there.​ ​​
​​​ ​Kiiiind of an L because that ​ ​​
​​ ​means he's closer to the bathroom.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahhh....​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm sitting here at the dining room.​ ​​
​​​ ​Biker-Man, what's your name?​ ​​
​​​ ​Bryce!​ ​​
​​​ ​WooOOooOowwww​ ​​
​​​ ​Biker-Man Bryce!​ ​​
​​​ ​He said he can cook.​ ​​
​​​ ​I just hope in the end that... ​ ​​
​​ ​we split.​ ​​
​​​ ​You know what I mean?​ ​​
​​​ ​That's what I want to happen.​ ​​
​​​ ​A hundred percent.​ ​​
​​​ ​Would I, would I not steal?​ ​​
​​​ ​Strongly, strongly leaning towards stealing.​ ​​
​​​ ​Regardless of Bryce's plan,​ ​​
​​​ ​Alison seems completely unfazed.​ ​​
​​​ ​I genuinely have nothing ​ ​​
​​ ​to complain about.​ ​​
​​​ ​I felt like in the sky I always had ​ ​​
​​ ​something to complain about.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is two times for you now?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​She has already had that 250,000 dollars.​ ​​
​​​ ​I came here to make money.​ ​​
​​​ ​What if I hear you sleep-talk, ​ ​​
​​ ​and in your dream, you're like,​ ​​
​​​ ​"I'm stealing the monneeeyyy."​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't believe me.​ ​​
​​​ ​HA HA HA!​ ​​
​​​ ​I feeeel like Bryce is trying to...​ ​​
​​​ ​make himself seem super... trustworthy​ ​​
​​​ ​so that he could steal the money.​ ​​
​​​ ​So curious how he would react,​ ​​
​​​ ​Alison decided to test him.​ ​​
​​​ ​OOHhHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​Run.​ ​​
​​​ ​RuUUUN?!​ ​​
​​​ ​NOOoooO!​ ​​
​​​ ​Out of context, two strangers ​ ​​
​​ ​chained together​ ​​
​​​ ​throwing things at each other... ​ ​​
​​ ​sounds bad.​ ​​
​​​ ​But seeing how they're laughing, I'm ​ ​​
​​ ​gonna assume it's okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​No! Oh, oh, oh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, that was a good catch!​ ​​
​​​ ​At least they're having fun. Let's see ​ ​​
​​ ​if all of that changes in two days.​ ​​
​​​ ​You'll see what I'm talking about.​ ​​
​​​ ​two hundred fifty thousand dollars ​ ​​
​​ ​is a lot of money,​ ​​
​​​ ​heh heh ha haa!​ ​​
​​​ ​but I still don't think I could do it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, I can sit here and say, ​ ​​
​​ ​"You're not going to steal that money,"​ ​​
​​​ ​aaaalll day long.​ ​​
​​​ ​You could be lying to me ​ ​​
​​ ​and I still have to hope.​ ​​
​​​ ​It is now time to change everything.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ayyee yo, aye yo, hey yo...​ ​​
​​​ ​What is that?​ ​​
​​​ ​A liiimmoooo?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohhhhhh my God.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll tell you when to open it back up.​ ​​
​​​ ​Jimmyyy?​ ​​
​​​ ​Why do you guys look like that?​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Uhhhh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Why do you think there's ​ ​​
​​ ​a limo right there?​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel like limos fit a lot of people.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep.​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe there's people?​ ​​
​​​ ​Before I explain what's going on...​ ​​
​​​ ​Does Nolan walking look ​ ​​
​​ ​awkward to anyone else?​ ​​
​​​ ​It looks extreeeemellly awkward.​ ​​
​​​ ​I, uh, its--its impressive.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm glad you said something.​ ​​
​​​ ​I said there'd be a twist on day five.​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on out.​ ​​
​​​ ​Did indeed.​ ​​
​​​ ​Send 'em out, Nolan!​ ​​
​​​ ​There's a cheerleader.​ ​​
​​​ ​A cheerleader? Let's goooo!​ ​​
​​​ ​There's a pregnant woman.​ ​​
​​​ ​Pregnant moooom!​ ​​
​​​ ​And a lawyer.​ ​​
​​​ ​Lawyer?​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay...​ ​​
​​​ ​Every five days, Alison,​ ​​
​​​ ​you are gonna ​ ​​
​​ ​be handcuffing yourself...​ ​​
​​​ ​...To a new stranger.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, I have to pick again?​ ​​
​​​ ​And then on day twenty five, ​ ​​
​​ ​I'm gonna bring them all back​ ​​
​​​ ​and you have to decide which one you ​ ​​
​​ ​can trust the most to not steal the money.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're not allowed to speak to them.​ ​​
​​​ ​You have to pick based on ​ ​​
​​ ​purely looks alone.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh my goodness, you-- you​ ​​
​​​ ​would do this to me.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna be so for real. I'm really ​ ​​
​​ ​not trusting the lawyer.​ ​​
​​​ ​Look at that grin.​ ​​
​​​ ​And then let's talk about... ​ ​​
​​ ​the pregnant woman.​ ​​
​​​ ​Obviously, pregnant women look very nice,​ ​​
​​​ ​but she also has a higher ​ ​​
​​ ​justification to steal the money from you.​ ​​
​​​ ​I was just about to say that.​ ​​
​​​ ​And then we have a college cheerleader.​ ​​
​​​ ​She probably has some student debt.​ ​​
​​​ ​You know how that goes.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahaa!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is SO hard!​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe that lawyer's rich.​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe he won a multi million ​ ​​
​​ ​dollar case​ ​​
​​​ ​and he doesn't even need the money.​ ​​
​​​ ​Look at him smirking!​ ​​
​​​ ​What's in the briefcase?​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know.​ ​​
​​​ ​Is he bringing it in with him?​ ​​
​​​ ​I actually don't know.​ ​​
​​​ ​There is a world where you go home ​ ​​
​​ ​with zero dollars.​ ​​
​​​ ​I wire you nothing.​ ​​
​​​ ​Who's it gonna be?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna go with the cheerleader.​ ​​
​​​ ​The cheerleader???​ ​​
​​​ ​All right, Cheerleader, ​ ​​
​​ ​come on up!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay! Ah ha ha ha ha!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hi! Nice to meet you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello! Hello!​ ​​
​​​ ​My name's Alison.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm Skyler. Nice to meet you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Nice to meet you...​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll see you on day thirty. Take care!​ ​​
​​​ ​Byyye!​ ​​
​​​ ​BYYYEEE!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Bye!​ ​​
​​​ ​They're gonna want to know. ​ ​​
​​ ​Have you two ever met before?​ ​​
​​​ ​No.​ ​​
​​​ ​Right away, there was a clear ​ ​​
​​ ​difference in camaraderie​ ​​
​​​ ​with Alison's new stranger.​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll just be everywhere together, ​ ​​
​​ ​twenty-four seven.​ ​​
​​​ ​Sounds awesome.​ ​​
​​​ ​Skyler brought these eye patches.​ ​​
​​​ ​Spa daaay.​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel like everybody that ​ ​​
​​ ​comes in here​ ​​
​​​ ​is gonna tell me that they wouldn't steal,​ ​​
​​​ ​and that they would split 250,000 dollars.​ ​​
​​​ ​She's probably like,​ ​​
​​​ ​"I don't trust ​ ​​
​​ ​that giiirl."​ ​​
​​​ ​And with a quarter of a million ​ ​​
​​ ​dollars on the line,​ ​​
​​​ ​Alison wanted to know if she really ​ ​​
​​ ​could trust her new stranger.​ ​​
​​​ ​I have a really good idea.​ ​​
​​​ ​What?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's both stand right here, back-to-back, ​ ​​
​​ ​and run away as fast as possible.​ ​​
​​​ ​Whyyyy?​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you serious?​ ​​
​​​ ​Pleaasee!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okaayyy....​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah hah hah hah!​ ​​
​​​ ​HA HA HA​ ​​
​​​ ​Ha ha haaa ha ha!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm happy they're having fun,​ ​​
​​​ ​but so far, they haven't discussed the ​ ​​
​​ ​whole "money" thing.​ ​​
​​​ ​We haven't really talked about trust ​ ​​
​​ ​or anything like that.​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel like it's more of been like, ​ ​​
​​ ​a genuine, juuust....​ ​​
​​​ ​friendship girl time.​ ​​
​​​ ​You know, the game is for her to trust me.​ ​​
​​​ ​So I'm just gonna kind of keep playing ​ ​​
​​ ​it like I have been.​ ​​
​​​ ​AHHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​aahhhhh!!​ ​​
​​​ ​LET'S GO PIRATES!​ ​​
​​​ ​heh heh heh...​ ​​
​​​ ​And the girls were actually starting ​ ​​
​​ ​to open up to each other.​ ​​
​​​ ​So if you won the money, like what ​ ​​
​​ ​would you plan on doing with it?​ ​​
​​​ ​I would go to my dad​ ​​
​​​ ​and be like, "I need to know​ ​​
​​​ ​how to invest in something."​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's say like, I didn't make a like ​ ​​
​​ ​big amount of money until I was like old...​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know if my dad's gonna ​ ​​
​​ ​be here or not​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't, I don't know. If I wait too late, ​ ​​
​​ ​then like...​ ​​
​​​ ​You wouldn't have that experience with ​ ​​
​​ ​your dad.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​But it seemed like Skyler was almost ​ ​​
​​ ​getting too comfortable with Allison.​ ​​
​​​ ​I only like mint chocolate chip ​ ​​
​​ ​when it's green.​ ​​
​​​ ​Me, too!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's going on the "pros" list. "She ​ ​​
​​ ​likes mint chocolate chip when it's green."​ ​​
​​​ ​Which caused her to ​ ​​
​​ ​make a huuuge mistake.​ ​​
​​​ ​One step closer to 250 K!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​WAIT​ ​​
​​​ ​two hundred FIFTY?!?​ ​​
​​​ ​AAAHHHH!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​HAH HAH HAH​ ​​
​​​ ​HAH HAH HAAAHH​ ​​
​​​ ​HAAHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahh haa haa ha!​ ​​
​​​ ​That was an accident!!​ ​​
​​​ ​OOoooh, I told my secret.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahh hahaa​ ​​
​​​ ​My secret.​ ​​
​​​ ​noooo!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh my God...​ ​​
​​​ ​She slipped up. She slipped up.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahh hee ha ha ha!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, wait. Stand on my knee.​ ​​
​​​ ​Skyler sitting in all the money she's ​ ​​
​​ ​gonna steeeaaall.​ ​​
​​​ ​OoOOoooh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Haa ha haa!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wrong answeeerr!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right, we're pulling up to the house.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's time for the day ten twist,​ ​​
​​​ ​which is actually bigger ​ ​​
​​ ​than the day five one.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's see what Allison thinks.​ ​​
​​​ ​Heeey, how's it going?​ ​​
​​​ ​Goood! We actually have a ​ ​​
​​ ​surprise for you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, wait--​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, really?​ ​​
​​​ ​Five. Six. Seven. Eight.​ ​​
​​​ ​CHEER​ ​​
​​​ ​FOR​ ​​
​​​ ​Mrrrrrr​ ​​
​​​ ​BEEAAAST​ ​​
​​​ ​WE​ ​​
​​​ ​KNOW​ ​​
​​​ ​HE'S THE​ ​​
​​​ ​KIIINDEEEST!​ ​​
​​​ ​ONWARD​ ​​
​​​ ​TOOO MOONEEYYY!​ ​​
​​​ ​Go Jimmy!​ ​​
​​​ ​AAHHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​YeaaAHHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay...​ ​​
​​​ ​OH! Whooaa!​ ​​
​​​ ​WWOOOO!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okaaayy!​ ​​
​​​ ​With the chain!​ ​​
​​​ ​It seems like you two are ​ ​​
​​ ​bonding pretty well.​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you think she's gonna ​ ​​
​​ ​split that money with you?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hee hee!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right, Sky.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here-- Nolan, can you yell?​ ​​
​​​ ​aaaaAAAAAaa!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Keep going, Nolan.​ ​​
​​​ ​AAAAAAaaaaa!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​aahhh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Keep going!​ ​​
​​​ ​WaAH! HAA HAA​ ​​
​​​ ​If she picked you, would ​ ​​
​​ ​you steal the money?​ ​​
​​​ ​Two hundred fifty ​ ​​
​​ ​grand's A LOT.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, you know, after five days of ​ ​​
​​ ​getting to know each other...​ ​​
​​​ ​Really?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes, yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know if I would trust this one.​ ​​
​​​ ​Haa hee hee hah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Alison, are you ready to meet your new ​ ​​
​​ ​strangers?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah. I'm ready.​ ​​
​​​ ​Seeeend​ ​​
​​​ ​out the paint.​ ​​
​​​ ​The PAINT??​ ​​
​​​ ​The red line is now gone, because...​ ​​
​​​ ​the next five days aren't ​ ​​
​​ ​going to be in this house...​ ​​
​​​ ​It's actually going to be somewhere else.​ ​​
​​​ ​NooOOOOoo!​ ​​
​​​ ​HAA HAA nooo way.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're joking!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, my God.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm kind of scared to get in there, ​ ​​
​​ ​but you know what?​ ​​
​​​ ​The rules are the rules.​ ​​
​​​ ​You should be excited.​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoooaaa, whhooa!​ ​​
​​​ ​What does that mean?​ ​​
​​​ ​Nolaaann!​ ​​
​​​ ​WwwooOOOP!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're not going to a new house. ​ ​​
​​ ​I'm not putting you BACK in the sky.​ ​​
​​​ ​You'll see in a moment.​ ​​
​​​ ​OHhhhh!​ ​​
​​​ ​In fact...​ ​​
​​​ ​We're putting Alison​ ​​
​​​ ​in a whole different video.​ ​​
​​​ ​Nooo wayyyy.​ ​​
​​​ ​No. Way.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're joking.​ ​​
​​​ ​Noo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ummm I see the grocery store!​ ​​
​​​ ​The grocery store.​ ​​
​​​ ​And I know what's in the grocery store.​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you talking about the ​ ​​
​​ ​grocery store where​ ​​
​​​ ​four people have to eat all the food ​ ​​
​​ ​in the store for one million dollars?​ ​​
​​​ ​...Yeeaah.​ ​​
​​​ ​That you might be joining for ​ ​​
​​ ​the next five days?​ ​​
​​​ ​Nooo WAYY!​ ​​
​​​ ​Waaiit... what???​ ​​
​​​ ​I hear the door opening. What could it be?​ ​​
​​​ ​I hear some chains.​ ​​
​​​ ​How's it going, boys?​ ​​
​​​ ​I brought you two friends!​ ​​
​​​ ​Heeey.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hiiii.​ ​​
​​​ ​To kick this off,​ ​​
​​​ ​Sky, can I see your hand?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep.​ ​​
​​​ ​While we're filming your ​ ​​
​​ ​grocery store video,​ ​​
​​​ ​we're also filming a video ​ ​​
​​ ​where every five days,​ ​​
​​​ ​Alison has to be chained ​ ​​
​​ ​to a new stranger.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, so you're about to bring in ​ ​​
​​ ​somebody else right now?​ ​​
​​​ ​No, it's gonna be one of us. ​ ​​
​​ ​Eldin, it's one of us!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sky, you are free.​ ​​
​​​ ​You can head out the grocery store. ​ ​​
​​ ​Take care.​ ​​
​​​ ​Bye Alison!​ ​​
​​​ ​Byyyeee!​ ​​
​​​ ​Bye, guysss.​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on over, Alison.​ ​​
​​​ ​You can ask ​ ​​
​​ ​whatever you want.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're gonna be handcuffed to ​ ​​
​​ ​one of these four guys​ ​​
​​​ ​for the next five days ​ ​​
​​ ​inside this grocery store.​ ​​
​​​ ​Which--​ ​​
​​​ ​while she's here, she can help ​ ​​
​​ ​you eat food...​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's gooo.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's goooo.​ ​​
​​​ ​Anybody...​ ​​
​​​ ​NOT want to be chained for ​ ​​
​​ ​two hundred fifty thousand dollars?​ ​​
​​​ ​What time do you wake up?​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, we're talking about 250,000 dollars. ​ ​​
​​ ​Not what time I wake up.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm down with 125,000 dollars.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, because you wouldn't steal the ​ ​​
​​ ​prize pool from her?​ ​​
​​​ ​Absolutely not.​ ​​
​​​ ​You wouldn't?​ ​​
​​​ ​No.​ ​​
​​​ ​Honestly, none of us would.​ ​​
​​​ ​Does anybody yap? ​ ​​
​​ ​Is anybody a talker?​ ​​
​​​ ​Pfftttt​ ​​
​​​ ​Dhhuuu heh heh heh​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll yap a lot.​ ​​
​​​ ​What's your thoughts on Juan?​ ​​
​​​ ​You've been really quiet. ​ ​​
​​ ​What are your thoughts?​ ​​
​​​ ​I-- I-- I'm okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right, Alison...​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooohh!!​ ​​
​​​ ​I need to knooowww...​ ​​
​​​ ​Who is it?​ ​​
​​​ ​I think I'm gonna go Juan.​ ​​
​​​ ​Juuaaan!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh my God.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, Juan.​ ​​
​​​ ​Sorry, Juan.​ ​​
​​​ ​And there we go.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're now part of their team.​ ​​
​​​ ​Welcome.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooohh my God...​ ​​
​​​ ​Welcome home!​ ​​
​​​ ​For the first time in our ​ ​​
​​ ​channel's history,​ ​​
​​​ ​we are merging ​ ​​
​​ ​two videos together.​ ​​
​​​ ​The Beast Multiverse.​ ​​
​​​ ​I worked blue collar, so I'm up at ​ ​​
​​ ​like five in the morning.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, actually, you guys have ​ ​​
​​ ​something in common!​ ​​
​​​ ​You both do construction.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, I'm a heavy equipment operator.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohhhh!​ ​​
​​​ ​I tear down buildings like this.​ ​​
​​​ ​You tear down buildings.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​And he builds buildings!​ ​​
​​​ ​I build the buildings. Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's GOO!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, this is great!​ ​​
​​​ ​Goooood mooorniiiiing.​ ​​
​​​ ​As part of their challenge,​ ​​
​​​ ​the grocery store contestants exercise ​ ​​
​​ ​to burn off all the food they're eating.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okaaaay.​ ​​
​​​ ​And after spending ten days ​ ​​
​​ ​in the cramped house,​ ​​
​​​ ​Alison was eager to join in.​ ​​
​​​ ​I haven't moved this much in days.​ ​​
​​​ ​I got so much energy, though.​ ​​
​​​ ​We're gonna burn the most calories.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ha ha haa!​ ​​
​​​ ​Alison also tried to help the boys eat ​ ​​
​​ ​the grocery food they didn't like.​ ​​
​​​ ​I woke up to her juicing cauliflower. ​ ​​
​​ ​She said her family loves doing this.​ ​​
​​​ ​There's only one ingredient.​ ​​
​​​ ​What's the ingredient?​ ​​
​​​ ​Cauliflower. We got this.​ ​​
​​​ ​We got this, Juan.​ ​​
​​​ ​WHAT theee heck?​ ​​
​​​ ​Eeeww, bro.​ ​​
​​​ ​AHHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​But Alison still had her own ​ ​​
​​ ​challenge to worry about,​ ​​
​​​ ​and she had to learn if she could ​ ​​
​​ ​trust another complete stranger.​ ​​
​​​ ​If you were to win the 125,000 dollars​ ​​
​​​ ​orrr possibly 250,000 dollars if you ​ ​​
​​ ​stole...​ ​​
​​​ ​I will tell you the truth:​ ​​
​​​ ​NEVER I steal anything.​ ​​
​​​ ​Never stole anything?​ ​​
​​​ ​Never stealing, no food,​ ​​
​​​ ​no money, nothing.​ ​​
​​​ ​How many kids do you have?​ ​​
​​​ ​I have six, six kids.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is all literally just ​ ​​
​​ ​for your family?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes. Yes. That's all.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's kind of how I feel, ​ ​​
​​ ​too because...​ ​​
​​​ ​my dad was recently ​ ​​
​​ ​diagnosed with dementia.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh, my God.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah. He took care of all of us.​ ​​
​​​ ​So my hope is...​ ​​
​​​ ​I can go give back to ​ ​​
​​ ​them because they need it like,​ ​​
​​​ ​more than I need it.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna tell him you said that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahh haa haa ha!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes!​ ​​
​​​ ​Juan... He does not have ​ ​​
​​ ​a bad bone in his body.​ ​​
​​​ ​He literally ​ ​​
​​ ​loves everyone.​ ​​
​​​ ​And he just reminds me of my dad.​ ​​
​​​ ​So after Juan, I got more ​ ​​
​​ ​strangers to be chained to.​ ​​
​​​ ​I trusted them.​ ​​
​​​ ​Like, I don't think ​ ​​
​​ ​that they would steal.​ ​​
​​​ ​Buuuut the goal is to find the ​ ​​
​​ ​most trustworthy.​ ​​
​​​ ​For Juan, that just means ​ ​​
​​ ​literally just be yourself.​ ​​
​​​ ​We're a good team.​ ​​
​​​ ​Heeeyy, look who it is!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's where my fiance went.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hi, baabyyy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Moments like this, I realize just...​ ​​
​​​ ​how weird our videos ​ ​​
​​ ​are sometimes-- Huh huh!​ ​​
​​​ ​What even is this?​ ​​
​​​ ​We got Juan over here ​ ​​
​​ ​chained to Alison,​ ​​
​​​ ​working out with my fiance.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't-- I don't know what's come of ​ ​​
​​ ​my channel.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait what do you think the next five ​ ​​
​​ ​days will be after this?​ ​​
​​​ ​I mean, part of me really hopes I'm ​ ​​
​​ ​not going back to that tiny house.​ ​​
​​​ ​So you want me to destroy ​ ​​
​​ ​that tiny house?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah. Please, I can't.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay. Here-- let me-- I'm gonna set ​ ​​
​​ ​the chain down.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oohhh.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ope, sorry. Uh, let me go see what I ​ ​​
​​ ​can cook up.​ ​​
​​​ ​"Cook up" ??​ ​​
​​​ ​Alison...​ ​​
​​​ ​are you ready to meet​ ​​
​​​ ​your next batch of strangers?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yesss.​ ​​
​​​ ​Send them in!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, no.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, no?​ ​​
​​​ ​OHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​WhatAATT?​ ​​
​​​ ​What in the world? OHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's what I'm talking 'bout.​ ​​
​​​ ​Woooo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Alison, what you are looking at​ ​​
​​​ ​is a fighter, a cowboy,​ ​​
​​​ ​and a sumo wrestler.​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you think, Alison?​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh, can I take a minute to, like, chat ​ ​​
​​ ​with the boys?​ ​​
​​​ ​No!​ ​​
​​​ ​Juan is now free.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you, Alison.​ ​​
​​​ ​Bye, Juan.​ ​​
​​​ ​Alison...​ ​​
​​​ ​Whooo...​ ​​
​​​ ​am I putting it on?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna have to go wiiiith...​ ​​
​​​ ​the cowboy.​ ​​
​​​ ​The cowboy?​ ​​
​​​ ​All riiiiight. Thank you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay. Stick out your right hand.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​I've never been so happy to be ​ ​​
​​ ​handcuffed before.​ ​​
​​​ ​Any last words, gentlemen?​ ​​
​​​ ​Bye!​ ​​
​​​ ​Love you!​ ​​
​​​ ​Love you Juan!​ ​​
​​​ ​Bye dude!​ ​​
​​​ ​Alison, it's time for the ​ ​​
​​ ​twist of the video.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, boy, oh boy, oh, boooyy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Take off your blindfolds.​ ​​
​​​ ​Replace them with these ​ ​​
​​ ​safety glasses.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's always a good sign.​ ​​
​​​ ​They haven't even turned around yet.​ ​​
​​​ ​Welcome to the next chapter of the ​ ​​
​​ ​Beast multiverse.​ ​​
​​​ ​We're about to drop A PLANE​ ​​
​​​ ​on your house.​ ​​
​​​ ​No you're not! WHAAAT??​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeppp!​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, you did say...​ ​​
​​​ ​You want me to destroy ​ ​​
​​ ​that tiny house?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah. Please.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​DROP THE PLANE!​ ​​
​​​ ​OHH my goodness!​ ​​
​​​ ​CRAAASHH​ ​​
​​​ ​OOohhhhh!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oooooooh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oooooooohhh ​ ​​
​​ ​my goodness.​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh hoooo!​ ​​
​​​ ​That was the loudest ​ ​​
​​ ​thing I've ever heard.​ ​​
​​​ ​Your house is now destroyed,​ ​​
​​​ ​and that's your guys's home ​ ​​
​​ ​for the next five days.​ ​​
​​​ ​What just happened?​ ​​
​​​ ​You're actually joking.​ ​​
​​​ ​You ever lived in a plane that ​ ​​
​​ ​crashed on a house before?​ ​​
​​​ ​... No.​ ​​
​​​ ​Now we have to paint a new circle.​ ​​
​​​ ​Daaaaaang.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, no! I've got it on my shoe!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait-- I've got it on my shoe!!​ ​​
​​​ ​OHHH nooo!​ ​​
​​​ ​HA HA HA HA HA​ ​​
​​​ ​Aaaand...​ ​​
​​​ ​with that​ ​​
​​​ ​you are now sealed into ​ ​​
​​ ​the circle for five days.​ ​​
​​​ ​Can I get you guys anything?​ ​​
​​​ ​I already know he's gonna say no.​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe an exercise bike.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll go get you one. I'll see ​ ​​
​​ ​you guys later.​ ​​
​​​ ​You ready?​ ​​
​​​ ​You ready, Jason?​ ​​
​​​ ​Following you, Als.​ ​​
​​​ ​Be carefuuuul! ​ ​​
​​ ​It's, like, really tilted.​ ​​
​​​ ​HooooooOOOOoooooollyy​ ​​
​​​ ​craaap.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know how we're ​ ​​
​​ ​gonna sleep at all.​ ​​
​​​ ​And you know what? ​ ​​
​​ ​This isn't my first rodeo.​ ​​
​​​ ​Y'all are gonna have a terrible night.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yee haw!​ ​​
​​​ ​HA HA HA HAAA!​ ​​
​​​ ​There's a slight slope, hah hah ha ha​ ​​
​​​ ​Just a slight angle going on.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's been a day since we ​ ​​
​​ ​dropped the plane.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's see how they're doing.​ ​​
​​​ ​Knock Knock!​ ​​
​​​ ​Who is it?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's Jimmy-- Ohhh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, welcome!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeahhh​ ​​
​​​ ​From the outside, it does not ​ ​​
​​ ​look this crooked. This is crrraazy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Is our cowboy over here ​ ​​
​​ ​getting half of $250,000?​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know.​ ​​
​​​ ​So if she picked you. You would split ​ ​​
​​ ​the money with her?​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh-- Uh-- I mean...​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh, uh, uh-- WHAT?!​ ​​
​​​ ​As of right now, I would. Yes, as of ​ ​​
​​ ​right now I would.​ ​​
​​​ ​Uhhh WHAT hee hee!​ ​​
​​​ ​Remember yesterday when I​ ​​
​​​ ​gave you one wish?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​Come outside.​ ​​
​​​ ​Nooo kiddiiiing!​ ​​
​​​ ​No waaaaayyy!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wooooowww.​ ​​
​​​ ​Is there anything else I can get you guys?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, I'm really bad at like, on the ​ ​​
​​ ​spot knowing because​ ​​
​​​ ​I never even think that this, like...​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Well then, you got everything ​ ​​
​​ ​you need.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll see you guys tomorrow.​ ​​
​​​ ​Na-- aha ha haaa!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right. Bye, Alisooonn!​ ​​
​​​ ​NO! NOOO! AHHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​Niiiiice!​ ​​
​​​ ​Chain's in the way!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ughh!​ ​​
​​​ ​You better peddle, by gooosh!​ ​​
​​​ ​AAHHHHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​You better peddle!​ ​​
​​​ ​Woohoo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Daaaaangg ugh!​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel bad for dropping a ​ ​​
​​ ​plane on their house.​ ​​
​​​ ​Majd-- send in ​ ​​
​​ ​the care package!!​ ​​
​​​ ​I heard you guys are hungry!​ ​​
​​​ ​Inside here I have some Feastables.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's gooo!​ ​​
​​​ ​AWWWHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​THAANK YOUU!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​First bite of a Feastables smore.​ ​​
​​​ ​Mmmmm!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's REAL good.​ ​​
​​​ ​Do I have any on my face?​ ​​
​​​ ​HEE HEE!​ ​​
​​​ ​So, what were you saying you would do ​ ​​
​​ ​with the money if you won?​ ​​
​​​ ​It would be like a kids cowboy camp.​ ​​
​​​ ​We would have sheep ​ ​​
​​ ​for the little kids​ ​​
​​​ ​and then have junior bulls​ ​​
​​​ ​for the 13 year old, 14 year old.​ ​​
​​​ ​That sounds expensive.​ ​​
​​​ ​And one thing I've been waiting ​ ​​
​​ ​for him to say​ ​​
​​​ ​and hoping he says,​ ​​
​​​ ​is that he will not ​ ​​
​​ ​steal the money.​ ​​
​​​ ​But if he's not ​ ​​
​​ ​able to say that,​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't think I'm going to be able to ​ ​​
​​ ​put him above the people​ ​​
​​​ ​that I've already been ​ ​​
​​ ​chained to.​ ​​
​​​ ​What would you do if you had ​ ​​
​​ ​a chance to win​ ​​
​​​ ​two hundred fifty thousand...​ ​​
​​​ ​or one hundred twenty ​ ​​
​​ ​five thousand?​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll see what happens.​ ​​
​​​ ​But with the start of Day 20,​ ​​
​​​ ​it's time for Alison to pick ​ ​​
​​ ​her last stranger.​ ​​
​​​ ​Alright, alriiiggght, alright!​ ​​
​​​ ​OOHH it's Majd! Woaaah!​ ​​
​​​ ​Today is day 20 for Alison. ​ ​​
​​ ​Day 5 for Jason.​ ​​
​​​ ​You know what that means.​ ​​
​​​ ​Bring out the strangers!​ ​​
​​​ ​We have a rock star.​ ​​
​​​ ​We have a fisherman.​ ​​
​​​ ​We have a professional ​ ​​
​​ ​basketball player.​ ​​
​​​ ​OooOOO! AHHH hoo hoo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Good options. Great options.​ ​​
​​​ ​So, Alison... who's it gonna be?​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay...​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna go wiiiith​ ​​
​​​ ​the pro basketball player.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's GGOOOOO!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okaaaayyy!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm ready, let's get it.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right, Jason, you're officially ​ ​​
​​ ​free to go.​ ​​
​​​ ​Bye, Jason.​ ​​
​​​ ​Good luck to you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Eat some sushi for me.​ ​​
​​​ ​I will, you'll do great.​ ​​
​​​ ​OOooohh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Official.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ey, we in this now!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yyaaaayyyy!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, and one more thing, Alison.​ ​​
​​​ ​We figured you guys need ​ ​​
​​ ​a little more space,​ ​​
​​​ ​so we're gonna ​ ​​
​​ ​expand your parameters.​ ​​
​​​ ​OOooOOhhh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, look at that finesse.​ ​​
​​​ ​Niceee.​ ​​
​​​ ​This feels wrong. ​ ​​
​​ ​This feels really wrong.​ ​​
​​​ ​For a second time, Alison will be ​ ​​
​​ ​going into another video with a stranger,​ ​​
​​​ ​the sequel to one of our ​ ​​
​​ ​most popular videos.​ ​​
​​​ ​where this couple is attempting to lose ​ ​​
​​ ​150 pounds before their wedding.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hiiiii!​ ​​
​​​ ​Heeey!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hi, guys.​ ​​
​​​ ​Alison, this is who you've been ​ ​​
​​ ​yelling at over there.​ ​​
​​​ ​You want to give them a tour?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, come on, guys.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm so excited!​ ​​
​​​ ​Welcome to your new home.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's gooo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Alison and Bri will get full access to ​ ​​
​​ ​everything here.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, it's so CUUUTTE!​ ​​
​​​ ​haa haa!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is the spot.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, this is nice.​ ​​
​​​ ​Can we use the shower?​ ​​
​​​ ​Y'all can use the shower.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohhh my God.​ ​​
​​​ ​I thought the grocery store ​ ​​
​​ ​was gonna be the biggest twist yet.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​And now I'm in another set!​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel fine. I feel great.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahh ha haa haa!​ ​​
​​​ ​You got lucky.​ ​​
​​​ ​Imma teach you how to be the next ​ ​​
​​ ​female Harlem Globetrotter.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think I'm gonna have to ​ ​​
​​ ​grow about a few inches.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, I'm an inch taller than you!!​ ​​
​​​ ​And then WALK,​ ​​
​​​ ​WALK,​ ​​
​​​ ​WALK...​ ​​
​​​ ​Ayyee!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oooh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeahhh!​ ​​
​​​ ​YeeeaaAHHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​Aye!​ ​​
​​​ ​So far, Brie seems like a ​ ​​
​​ ​really cool person.​ ​​
​​​ ​She loves to talk, ​ ​​
​​ ​super athletic,​ ​​
​​​ ​so I think I'll have a lot of fun here.​ ​​
​​​ ​Look at you.​ ​​
​​​ ​I know, perioood!​ ​​
​​​ ​Look at yoouuu, period, giiirl!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ha ha ha haa!​ ​​
​​​ ​ha ha haa!​ ​​
​​​ ​You know, I don't know her that well yet.​ ​​
​​​ ​And she's already won two ​ ​​
​​ ​hundred fifty thousand dollars.​ ​​
​​​ ​She's already won!​ ​​
​​​ ​At this point, she's gonna ​ ​​
​​ ​have to convince me​ ​​
​​​ ​to NOT take the 250.​ ​​
​​​ ​WOOOWWWW!​ ​​
​​​ ​Brie is already going for the steal.​ ​​
​​​ ​The question is:​ ​​
​​​ ​will Alison be able ​ ​​
​​ ​to sniff it out?​ ​​
​​​ ​We did a workout this morning,​ ​​
​​​ ​and Ohh. Myyy. Goodness.​ ​​
​​​ ​IIIIIII was dyyying.​ ​​
​​​ ​If you got money, what's the plan?​ ​​
​​​ ​Family first. My aunt, who's been ​ ​​
​​ ​homeless for a while.​ ​​
​​​ ​And I would just try to do my best to ​ ​​
​​ ​get her out of that situation.​ ​​
​​​ ​Like, this isn't about me.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is about them.​ ​​
​​​ ​YYEEAAHHHHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's goooOOOOO!​ ​​
​​​ ​First tryyy!!​ ​​
​​​ ​WOOOOOO!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel like... I've been myself.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm all about vibes​ ​​
​​​ ​We have good vibes. We have great vibes,​ ​​
​​​ ​like on the tennis court each day ​ ​​
​​ ​we've gotten better.​ ​​
​​​ ​You two got it! It's all y'all.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, we're having a lot of fun here,​ ​​
​​​ ​but if Brie wants a chance ​ ​​
​​ ​aaaat being the last person.​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel like I'm gonna need ​ ​​
​​ ​a little bit more.​ ​​
​​​ ​Like if I were her, I would dig in and ​ ​​
​​ ​see where my head's at​ ​​
​​​ ​Even though it's awkward, ​ ​​
​​ ​even though it's hard.​ ​​
​​​ ​I have a question for y'all.​ ​​
​​​ ​What's up?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah?​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't yell it, but...​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay. Hold on.​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you think I need ​ ​​
​​ ​to do to get her to trust me?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah. Just continue being yourself and ​ ​​
​​ ​being honest.​ ​​
​​​ ​So you would split a hundred percent?​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, between us... ​ ​​
​​ ​I would have to think.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, but and that's so valid.​ ​​
​​​ ​What would you do?​ ​​
​​​ ​Uuummm.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is-- this is up to you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hnnnhh!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's up to you.​ ​​
​​​ ​And with Alison's decision looming. I ​ ​​
​​ ​wanted to check in with both of them.​ ​​
​​​ ​I've noticed she hasn't said she ​ ​​
​​ ​wouldn't steal the money.​ ​​
​​​ ​No, I have not got the words from her. ​ ​​
​​ ​Which makes me question a little bit.​ ​​
​​​ ​What can do to make her ​ ​​
​​ ​believe you more?​ ​​
​​​ ​Trust you more?​ ​​
​​​ ​Dang, that's a great question.​ ​​
​​​ ​And with her time running out,​ ​​
​​​ ​our talk was the final push Brie ​ ​​
​​ ​needed to execute her plan.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm a competitor, aaaannd​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm about to make her ​ ​​
​​ ​know for sure that...​ ​​
​​​ ​she can trust me.​ ​​
​​​ ​Fingers will be crossed.​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel like you've gotten to ​ ​​
​​ ​know me enough​ ​​
​​​ ​to know that I'm a good person.​ ​​
​​​ ​And I, I care about people, and I ​ ​​
​​ ​never break promises.​ ​​
​​​ ​I didn't even show you this,​ ​​
​​​ ​but I literally, I literally have a ​ ​​
​​ ​tattoo that says, "promise."​ ​​
​​​ ​Daaaanng!​ ​​
​​​ ​So this is me saying:​ ​​
​​​ ​I promise that I would not take ​ ​​
​​ ​money from you.​ ​​
​​​ ​If I picked you, then it's one ​ ​​
​​ ​thousand percent guaranteed...​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​...win?​ ​​
​​​ ​I promise.​ ​​
​​​ ​She's actually the first stranger​ ​​
​​​ ​to say she promises ​ ​​
​​ ​she will not steal​ ​​
​​​ ​I do think if I pick her, it's a ​ ​​
​​ ​guaranteed win.​ ​​
​​​ ​The breaks and promises.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aaaannd... this tattoo might have to go.​ ​​
​​​ ​I might have to get that removed.​ ​​
​​​ ​But with one day until her big decision,​ ​​
​​​ ​things only became harder for Alison.​ ​​
​​​ ​It feels unfair to the people I've been ​ ​​
​​ ​chained to that I can only pick one​ ​​
​​​ ​and I just don't like that at all,​ ​​
​​​ ​because I feel like a lot of ​ ​​
​​ ​these people... I truly do trust.​ ​​
​​​ ​Guys....​ ​​
​​​ ​So like...​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know ​ ​​
​​ ​what to do.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is gonna affect people's lives.​ ​​
​​​ ​And I've heard everybody's stories​ ​​
​​​ ​and everybody's stories seem ​ ​​
​​ ​so valid and stuff.​ ​​
​​​ ​So now I'm just like...​ ​​
​​​ ​ohhh my God.​ ​​
​​​ ​Every choice you make will ​ ​​
​​ ​be the right choice.​ ​​
​​​ ​No decision is a ​ ​​
​​ ​wrong decision.​ ​​
​​​ ​So I wouldn't worry about that aspect.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​It is who you trust.​ ​​
​​​ ​Like that gut feeling.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm literally just gonna go with the ​ ​​
​​ ​flow tomorrow​ ​​
​​​ ​and probably be really freaking surprised.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right. It's the big day.​ ​​
​​​ ​Today's the day​ ​​
​​​ ​Alison decides who to trust ​ ​​
​​ ​a quarter of a million dollars with.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Ah haaa!​ ​​
​​​ ​Just kidding!​ ​​
​​​ ​You'll have five days ​ ​​
​​ ​to decide.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, thank God.​ ​​
​​​ ​It'll make sense after you follow me ​ ​​
​​ ​into the limo out front.​ ​​
​​​ ​Goooosh.​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you ready to make arguably the ​ ​​
​​ ​biggest decision of your life?​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel like from my reaction, you can ​ ​​
​​ ​tell the answer is no.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here's a blindfold, Alison.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohhhkayyyy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, lord.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here's a blindfold.​ ​​
​​​ ​If you guys don't mind putting that on, ​ ​​
​​ ​that'd be great.​ ​​
​​​ ​Byyyyeeee!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're gonna do greaaatt!​ ​​
​​​ ​Good luck. Let's see what she decides.​ ​​
​​​ ​hhhuuuuuhhhhh​ ​​
​​​ ​What in the world?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm a competitor.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is not a real place.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is a challenge. ​ ​​
​​ ​I made promises to her.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know, Alison. ​ ​​
​​ ​250K is a lot of money​ ​​
​​​ ​Hn hn hn hn....​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel like there's a right choice. ​ ​​
​​ ​That is fair and makes sense.​ ​​
​​​ ​Definitely felt not a huge connection ​ ​​
​​ ​to her... at all.​ ​​
​​​ ​We're definitely two different people.​ ​​
​​​ ​I so happy for her.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't want to ​ ​​
​​ ​steal any money.​ ​​
​​​ ​I want to split it.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is hard. ​ ​​
​​ ​I feel bad heh heh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Everybody take off your blindfolds.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello, everyoooone.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hello Alison.​ ​​
​​​ ​In front of Alison is all the ​ ​​
​​ ​strangers​ ​​
​​​ ​that she has been handcuffed to.​ ​​
​​​ ​If you're wondering how Juan's here,​ ​​
​​​ ​it's actually because we're in the ​ ​​
​​ ​back of the grocery store,​ ​​
​​​ ​so Juan's doing two videos ​ ​​
​​ ​at once right now.​ ​​
​​​ ​You know, I honestly wasn't expecting ​ ​​
​​ ​it this fast. I thought I had five more days.​ ​​
​​​ ​You do have five more days.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohhh.​ ​​
​​​ ​To make your decision.​ ​​
​​​ ​You see, starting now​ ​​
​​​ ​at any point you can ​ ​​
​​ ​press this button​ ​​
​​​ ​and start sending people home, oorrrr​ ​​
​​​ ​you can take up to another five ​ ​​
​​ ​days to get to know them.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ask any other questions you want.​ ​​
​​​ ​...Ohh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wooow.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay...​ ​​
​​​ ​well, there was one other thing ​ ​​
​​ ​I had to explain.​ ​​
​​​ ​But I mean, she already hit it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Can we put that in reverse?​ ​​
​​​ ​N-- no,​ ​​
​​​ ​Umm...​ ​​
​​​ ​the last thing I was gonna say:​ ​​
​​​ ​All five of them​ ​​
​​​ ​already made their decision​ ​​
​​​ ​on whether or not they would ​ ​​
​​ ​split or steal the money with you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoever you eliminate first​ ​​
​​​ ​will get ten thousand dollars.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here, Nolan, can you bring it in?​ ​​
​​​ ​Huh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohhh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okayyyy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Nolan, I like that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeahhh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah. Thank you, Nolan.​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoever you eliminate second​ ​​
​​​ ​will get twenty thousand dollars.​ ​​
​​​ ​Third, thirty thousand dollars...​ ​​
​​​ ​Fourth, forty thousand dollars.​ ​​
​​​ ​So the order in which ​ ​​
​​ ​you eliminate them​ ​​
​​​ ​actually matters quite a bit.​ ​​
​​​ ​And why I was gonna give you up ​ ​​
​​ ​to five days to think about it​ ​​
​​​ ​until she just, uhh--​ ​​
​​​ ​hit the button.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, I can't take that back now, ​ ​​
​​ ​okay--​ ​​
​​​ ​Pliers.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Alright!​ ​​
​​​ ​Everything's happening quick. ​ ​​
​​ ​Alison just has no patience!​ ​​
​​​ ​The fun part is too, when I cut 'em, ​ ​​
​​ ​we'll reveal what their decision was.​ ​​
​​​ ​That is fun. That is fun.​ ​​
​​​ ​I honestly, it makes ​ ​​
​​ ​me feel better​ ​​
​​​ ​knowing that every single one ​ ​​
​​ ​of you is walking away with something.​ ​​
​​​ ​I mean, at the end of the day, you guys ​ ​​
​​ ​were all here for only five days​ ​​
​​​ ​and you're still getting something.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ten thousand dollars in five days--​ ​​
​​​ ​That is a blessing.​ ​​
​​​ ​So is a hundred twenty five.​ ​​
​​​ ​Or two hundred fifty ​ ​​
​​ ​thousand dollars.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is-- this is ​ ​​
​​ ​huge for them.​ ​​
​​​ ​We can start on the left side.​ ​​
​​​ ​Did you steal the money?​ ​​
​​​ ​I did not.​ ​​
​​​ ​We promised each other ​ ​​
​​ ​we wouldn't do it​ ​​
​​​ ​if she had the option to do it.​ ​​
​​​ ​We said we wouldn't.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​I do believe you did not steal. I ​ ​​
​​ ​hundred percent believe it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Sky...​ ​​
​​​ ​did you steal the money?​ ​​
​​​ ​No.​ ​​
​​​ ​What about Juan?​ ​​
​​​ ​Did you steal the money?​ ​​
​​​ ​No, no.​ ​​
​​​ ​No?​ ​​
​​​ ​Juan never steals.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​Mr. Cowboy, what do you want to ​ ​​
​​ ​say to her?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, Alison.​ ​​
​​​ ​Uhh, I appreciate you ​ ​​
​​ ​trusting me.​ ​​
​​​ ​She hasn't​ ​​
​​​ ​chosen to trust you yet.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, that's true, that's true.​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you think he stole the money?​ ​​
​​​ ​You know,​ ​​
​​​ ​honestly, you're the one ​ ​​
​​ ​person I had my doubts about.​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoooaaa.​ ​​
​​​ ​And I have to be honest.​ ​​
​​​ ​That hurts.​ ​​
​​​ ​I mean, did you steal the money?​ ​​
​​​ ​No, I did not.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aaannd I'm a bad liar,​ ​​
​​​ ​so I didn't wanna pretend ​ ​​
​​ ​in the beginning.​ ​​
​​​ ​And then her think that I ​ ​​
​​ ​was lying to her.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, I believe him.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, Brie?​ ​​
​​​ ​I think these are some amazing ​ ​​
​​ ​human beings over here.​ ​​
​​​ ​Just by the looks of you guys, ​ ​​
​​ ​I've heard y'alls story.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't think anybody's life's​ ​​
​​​ ​moooore important.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think it's just a matter of who ​ ​​
​​ ​she connected with the most.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a tough decision. How do you decide?​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, I think I go with least ​ ​​
​​ ​trustworthy to most trustworthy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here you go.​ ​​
​​​ ​So the person you're ​ ​​
​​ ​about to choose,​ ​​
​​​ ​you trust the least.​ ​​
​​​ ​Correct.​ ​​
​​​ ​I have to pick you because you were ​ ​​
​​ ​the only person​ ​​
​​​ ​in the lineup that did not say​ ​​
​​​ ​flat out that they would ​ ​​
​​ ​not take the money.​ ​​
​​​ ​That being said, it's like...​ ​​
​​​ ​Ten thousand dollars?​ ​​
​​​ ​How many bulls can you get with that?​ ​​
​​​ ​Hee haa haa!​ ​​
​​​ ​I have to remember, Alison's already ​ ​​
​​ ​won a lot of money.​ ​​
​​​ ​I didn't come to win second. ​ ​​
​​ ​I came to win first.​ ​​
​​​ ​Reveal his decision.​ ​​
​​​ ​Whooooaaaa!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​You chose to steal the money from her?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah. When I said...​ ​​
​​​ ​unless things change.​ ​​
​​​ ​Daaang. He he hee hee!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's craaazzyyy.​ ​​
​​​ ​There would have been a world.​ ​​
​​​ ​If he was last remaining.​ ​​
​​​ ​He would have taken ​ ​​
​​ ​all 250 grand.​ ​​
​​​ ​And you would have been ​ ​​
​​ ​here for nothing.​ ​​
​​​ ​BUT you sniffed it out.​ ​​
​​​ ​Haa haa haaa...​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoa!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm, like, remembering everything.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ahhh hah HAH Hahhh...​ ​​
​​​ ​And I'm like wooowww.​ ​​
​​​ ​You played the game good. ​ ​​
​​ ​But I played the game great.​ ​​
​​​ ​You did.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna give you some ​ ​​
​​ ​time with the other four.​ ​​
​​​ ​Befooore I knew​ ​​
​​​ ​everybody was gonna get money,​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh huh​ ​​
​​​ ​you were gonna win.​ ​​
​​​ ​Soooo I was gonna make ​ ​​
​​ ​it your decision.​ ​​
​​​ ​If I could help them out more by ​ ​​
​​ ​giving them more money.​ ​​
​​​ ​$20,000​ ​​
​​​ ​$30,000​ ​​
​​​ ​and $40,000​ ​​
​​​ ​It's up to you​ ​​
​​​ ​which one you want.​ ​​
​​​ ​I trust you the most.​ ​​
​​​ ​Alll right.​ ​​
​​​ ​Did you guys miss me?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh whaat, you didn't--​ ​​
​​​ ​You didn't even say hi!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hi. How are you?​ ​​
​​​ ​Good.​ ​​
​​​ ​I`ve been waiting all day for that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh yeah, I can tell.​ ​​
​​​ ​Bring in the 20,000 dollars.​ ​​
​​​ ​YeaaHHHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thanks Nolan.​ ​​
​​​ ​The person you're about to save.​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you think they stole ​ ​​
​​ ​the money from you?​ ​​
​​​ ​I honestly think they stole the money.​ ​​
​​​ ​You think Brie stole the money from you?​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know.​ ​​
​​​ ​There's only one way to find out.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, why do you think it's me?​ ​​
​​​ ​My biggest thing is I ​ ​​
​​ ​don't want to send Juan home​ ​​
​​​ ​and then see a red light.​ ​​
​​​ ​I want to make sure all the ​ ​​
​​ ​red lights are gone.​ ​​
​​​ ​Because if I send Juan home ​ ​​
​​ ​and see a red light,​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm going to be really upset.​ ​​
​​​ ​You'd have done this thirty day ​ ​​
​​ ​video for nothing.​ ​​
​​​ ​hnn hmmph​ ​​
​​​ ​Brie what do you ​ ​​
​​ ​want to say to her?​ ​​
​​​ ​She's calling you a liar.​ ​​
​​​ ​She's calling me a liar!​ ​​
​​​ ​Listen we gonna find out.​ ​​
​​​ ​I know I made promises to her, but...​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel like sometimes you gotta ​ ​​
​​ ​break the promiiiisse.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​So I win.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aaahhhh...​ ​​
​​​ ​Brie...​ ​​
​​​ ​decided to steal the ​ ​​
​​ ​money from you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Brie, what about your tattoo?​ ​​
​​​ ​Sticking to the promise ​ ​​
​​ ​I make myself and my family.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's what it really stands for.​ ​​
​​​ ​But, you know, I have to ​ ​​
​​ ​make it sound a little more interesting.​ ​​
​​​ ​Saw that one coming.​ ​​
​​​ ​Saw it coming for sure.​ ​​
​​​ ​NnnnooooOOOO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​You felt it, too!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yep!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeaahhh​ ​​
​​​ ​There you go.​ ​​
​​​ ​I ain't mad at it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Everyone say goodbye to Brie.​ ​​
​​​ ​Bye Brieeee​ ​​
​​​ ​Byyye.​ ​​
​​​ ​Goodbye.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, hold it down. Its been real.​ ​​
​​​ ​And now three of you remain.​ ​​
​​​ ​One of which will split ​ ​​
​​ ​a quarter of a million dollars.​ ​​
​​​ ​Can I... uhhh...​ ​​
​​​ ​OH!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh....​ ​​
​​​ ​Bring in the money, Nolan!​ ​​
​​​ ​What you say right now ​ ​​
​​ ​is very important, because...​ ​​
​​​ ​this could literally decide ​ ​​
​​ ​whether you go home with 30 grand,​ ​​
​​​ ​125 grand...​ ​​
​​​ ​or 250 grand.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know ​ ​​
​​ ​what you guys chose.​ ​​
​​​ ​HOPEFULLY not 250 grand!​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you want to say to Alison?​ ​​
​​​ ​This might be your last chance to ​ ​​
​​ ​talk to her, one on one.​ ​​
​​​ ​Promising and swearing doesn't ​ ​​
​​ ​mean anything.​ ​​
​​​ ​Everybody just lies.​ ​​
​​​ ​So, I mean,​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel like I did everything I can ​ ​​
​​ ​to make you trust me.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm not a big beggar or or like, ​ ​​
​​ ​you know what I'm saying? So...​ ​​
​​​ ​That's all I have.​ ​​
​​​ ​But I'm going to be your ​ ​​
​​ ​friend either way.​ ​​
​​​ ​What did you choose?​ ​​
​​​ ​I hit green.​ ​​
​​​ ​I could even say the ​ ​​
​​ ​reason why I hit green.​ ​​
​​​ ​Tell us.​ ​​
​​​ ​In front of that camera.​ ​​
​​​ ​But, you know, I took your word.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think you took mine.​ ​​
​​​ ​And karma comes ​ ​​
​​ ​back tenfold.​ ​​
​​​ ​So...​ ​​
​​​ ​Whooaa.​ ​​
​​​ ​that's all I really care about.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's a powerful sentence.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​If he means that, then that seems like ​ ​​
​​ ​a pretty honest sentence.​ ​​
​​​ ​My gut​ ​​
​​​ ​is telling me that ​ ​​
​​ ​you did not steal.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a big decision, Alison!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a really big decision.​ ​​
​​​ ​And after what we've witnessed, it like, ​ ​​
​​ ​makes me a little uneasy still.​ ​​
​​​ ​Because you never know ​ ​​
​​ ​what can happen.​ ​​
​​​ ​You never know what somebody's ​ ​​
​​ ​truly thinking.​ ​​
​​​ ​250 K!!!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​But that being said, I still feel like ​ ​​
​​ ​I kind of have it figured out,​ ​​
​​​ ​and I'm comfortable with what I'm ​ ​​
​​ ​about to do next,​ ​​
​​​ ​hoping that it's the right decision.​ ​​
​​​ ​And I really do think it is.​ ​​
​​​ ​Whaa I--​ ​​
​​​ ​what is she about to do?​ ​​
​​​ ​Juan.​ ​​
​​​ ​No, Alison!​ ​​
​​​ ​Noooo!​ ​​
​​​ ​In your head, you think Juan ​ ​​
​​ ​didn't steal the money?​ ​​
​​​ ​You're still gonna eliminate him?​ ​​
​​​ ​I am.​ ​​
​​​ ​And the reason I'm going to ​ ​​
​​ ​eliminate Juan is because​ ​​
​​​ ​him and I both talked about it.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll be okay for me.​ ​​
​​​ ​Whatever you, whatever ​ ​​
​​ ​your number you give me,​ ​​
​​​ ​that be okay for me.​ ​​
​​​ ​That be okay. ​ ​​
​​ ​I happy, I happy with you?​ ​​
​​​ ​He said he's good when he ​ ​​
​​ ​gets out of here.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, assuming he eats everything in ​ ​​
​​ ​the grocery store.​ ​​
​​​ ​I know Juan!! He's gonna eat ​ ​​
​​ ​everything in that grocery store.​ ​​
​​​ ​And now this is an act from Juan and I ​ ​​
​​ ​to help these two out more.​ ​​
​​​ ​So you didn't even want to win.​ ​​
​​​ ​You wanted to give them the ​ ​​
​​ ​opportunity to win?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes, yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know if I've ever had ​ ​​
​​ ​someone sacrifice themselves​ ​​
​​​ ​like Juan is doing right now.​ ​​
​​​ ​NOOOOO!​ ​​
​​​ ​They're literally YELLING ​ ​​
​​ ​in the grocery store!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Reveal his results!​ ​​
​​​ ​YAAAYYY!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​I happy, I happy its me!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Guys!​ ​​
​​​ ​The green light works! It works!​ ​​
​​​ ​It works! I was a little ​ ​​
​​ ​worried for a second.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait! why are you cheering?​ ​​
​​​ ​You just lost 125 grand, ​ ​​
​​ ​potentially.​ ​​
​​​ ​I really hope not. I really, ​ ​​
​​ ​really hope not!​ ​​
​​​ ​I think I make good judgment, ​ ​​
​​ ​so far I haven't been wrong.​ ​​
​​​ ​And if I'm right,​ ​​
​​​ ​the next two lights ​ ​​
​​ ​will be green.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you so much.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh my gosh. There you go.​ ​​
​​​ ​Juan was an honest man.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you Juuaann!​ ​​
​​​ ​Head back to the grocery store.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thanks Juan!​ ​​
​​​ ​Bye Juaaan!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Good luuuck.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think you just played probably ​ ​​
​​ ​one of the best​ ​​
​​​ ​beast games, to be honest ​ ​​
​​ ​with you.​ ​​
​​​ ​How did I do that?​ ​​
​​​ ​I couldn't, like, speak it ​ ​​
​​ ​because she was here.​ ​​
​​​ ​She was so different.​ ​​
​​​ ​So different.​ ​​
​​​ ​and I could sense something was up.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm like, "Why is she not being ​ ​​
​​ ​the same person?"​ ​​
​​​ ​But you were ​ ​​
​​ ​the same person.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's been over 24 hours and Alison ​ ​​
​​ ​still hasn't hit the button.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, I had time to sleep ​ ​​
​​ ​the night throuugghh.​ ​​
​​​ ​Think about it a ​ ​​
​​ ​little bit more.​ ​​
​​​ ​Guys, I have other videos to film.​ ​​
​​​ ​I didn't think this would take so long​ ​​
​​​ ​Hah hah hah ha haa!​ ​​
​​​ ​I will feel better going home​ ​​
​​​ ​knowing I took time to ​ ​​
​​ ​think about it​ ​​
​​​ ​and make a good decision.​ ​​
​​​ ​Regardless of who Alison ​ ​​
​​ ​sends home next,​ ​​
​​​ ​there is still a chance she walks ​ ​​
​​ ​out of here with nothing.​ ​​
​​​ ​One of you​ ​​
​​​ ​is about to win ​ ​​
​​ ​40,000 dollars​ ​​
​​​ ​and one of you​ ​​
​​​ ​is about to win one ​ ​​
​​ ​hundred twenty five​ ​​
​​​ ​to two hundred fifty ​ ​​
​​ ​thousand dollars.​ ​​
​​​ ​But I'm curious,​ ​​
​​​ ​Sky, what do you think?​ ​​
​​​ ​Looks pretty appealing.​ ​​
​​​ ​She's saying she doesn't ​ ​​
​​ ​even want that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, I didn't, I didn't say that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Tchhh huh huh!​ ​​
​​​ ​hee hah hah heehh!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right well, you don't ​ ​​
​​ ​need this anymore.​ ​​
​​​ ​Pliers me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohhhh​ ​​
​​​ ​the plieeeerrrs agaaaain.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh boy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Alison...​ ​​
​​​ ​if you choose wrong, it could ​ ​​
​​ ​cost you everything.​ ​​
​​​ ​I was hoping there wasn't a wrong ​ ​​
​​ ​answer in the room.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm not gonna say anything.​ ​​
​​​ ​There's no wrong answers, guys. ​ ​​
​​ ​There's no wrong answers.​ ​​
​​​ ​I thought long and hard about this.​ ​​
​​​ ​Obviously, we stayed a whole ​ ​​
​​ ​'nother night in here​ ​​
​​​ ​because I didn't want to ​ ​​
​​ ​make the wrong choice.​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanted to make sure I was ​ ​​
​​ ​choosing wisely​ ​​
​​​ ​and to be honest, I really think ​ ​​
​​ ​that both of these people​ ​​
​​​ ​will have a green light.​ ​​
​​​ ​So that made it a little ​ ​​
​​ ​more difficult.​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you do when you ​ ​​
​​ ​trust both of them and-​ ​​
​​​ ​**FALLS**​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​Nolan I was in the ​ ​​
​​ ​middle of talking!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sorry.​ ​​
​​​ ​I- I think there's a light bulb that ​ ​​
​​ ​you should change over there.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​You don't want me to... ​ ​​
​​ ​pick the money up-​ ​​
​​​ ​No, no, no, no you should just...​ ​​
​​​ ​You've done enough.​ ​​
​​​ ​I appreciate- uh, you're a great guy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Bye.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah...​ ​​
​​​ ​It's not- yeah. Right there. ​ ​​
​​ ​Thank you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Trying to find the curtains behind here.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah yeah. No no, you're good.​ ​​
​​​ ​AHEM. Anyways.​ ​​
​​​ ​Anyways...​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm dying to know.​ ​​
​​​ ​I know you are.​ ​​
​​​ ​I want to know who she's choosing.​ ​​
​​​ ​Go for it Alison!​ ​​
​​​ ​I gotta dig deeper.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ay, yo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Tryna remind myself, what ​ ​​
​​ ​we're in here for.​ ​​
​​​ ​It is a game about trust.​ ​​
​​​ ​One step closer to 250K!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, 250!?​ ​​
​​​ ​Sorry, Bryce. I have to- choose her.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh my gosh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Before you say anything,​ ​​
​​​ ​do you want to see ​ ​​
​​ ​what he chose?​ ​​
​​​ ​I do.​ ​​
​​​ ​Be honest.​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you think he picked?​ ​​
​​​ ​I think it's green.​ ​​
​​​ ​He wouldn't be ​ ​​
​​ ​here if I thought it was red,​ ​​
​​​ ​because I would've had Juan ​ ​​
​​ ​here in his place.​ ​​
​​​ ​So there's no world that ​ ​​
​​ ​this is about to be red?​ ​​
​​​ ​There's no world.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay...​ ​​
​​​ ​Reveal the results!​ ​​
​​​ ​HA HAA HAA​ ​​
​​​ ​So, guys, there is a world.​ ​​
​​​ ​And it's this one. The one ​ ​​
​​ ​we're living in.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh, you're dead.​ ​​
​​​ ​Right now.​ ​​
​​​ ​YOU'RE JOKING!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is that real? Okay, ​ ​​
​​ ​turn the green light on now.​ ​​
​​​ ​No green light.​ ​​
​​​ ​Woooow.​ ​​
​​​ ​You. Owe. Juan. An apology.​ ​​
​​​ ​That- I do feel bad about.​ ​​
​​​ ​No, actually.​ ​​
​​​ ​Haa ha ha​ ​​
​​​ ​Is this the part where ​ ​​
​​ ​he leaves?​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you want him to leave?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​40,000 dollars in cash. Bryce, you've ​ ​​
​​ ​been eliminated.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yay, guys! Wow! It's over.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well. I mean, there's a world where ​ ​​
​​ ​every contestant minus Juan,​ ​​
​​​ ​chose to steal from you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hahhh...​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll see.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hn hnn...​ ​​
​​​ ​I scared.​ ​​
​​​ ​Every single decision has been in ​ ​​
​​ ​Alison's hands.​ ​​
​​​ ​Every five days she chose ​ ​​
​​ ​who to pair with,​ ​​
​​​ ​she chose who went ​ ​​
​​ ​home and what order.​ ​​
​​​ ​Alison has been in control ​ ​​
​​ ​this entire video.​ ​​
​​​ ​And it all led to this moment, ​ ​​
​​ ​right here.​ ​​
​​​ ​Alison, when that curtain drops,​ ​​
​​​ ​if Sky's there, and the money's there​ ​​
​​​ ​you're splitting it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​But if there's no Sky and no money,​ ​​
​​​ ​you're getting nothing.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wooow.​ ​​
​​​ ​And you wasted this entire time.​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you think every single person ​ ​​
​​ ​besides Juan tried to steal from you?​ ​​
​​​ ​I- I'm like, really nervous after the ​ ​​
​​ ​last situation.​ ​​
​​​ ​But I just still feel like​ ​​
​​​ ​she split the money.​ ​​
​​​ ​[nervous noises]​ ​​
​​​ ​We're about to find out.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm so scared I'm-​ ​​
​​​ ​All right.​ ​​
​​​ ​Three.​ ​​
​​​ ​Two.​ ​​
​​​ ​One.​ ​​
​​​ ​AAAHHHHHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​You guys are splitting the money!​ ​​
​​​ ​AHH HA HA HA​ ​​
​​​ ​Bro I was actually so scared.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're joking!!​ ​​
​​​ ​YEAAHHH!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​HAA HAA HAA!​ ​​
​​​ ​You are both going ​ ​​
​​ ​home with​ ​​
​​​ ​a hundred twenty five ​ ​​
​​ ​THOUSAND dollars in cash​ ​​
​​​ ​YAAaaaYYY!​ ​​
​​​ ​YEAHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sometimes strangers, are just friends ​ ​​
​​ ​you haven't met yet.​ ​​
​​​ ​Congratulations.​ ​​
​​​ ​YAYYY!​ ​​
​​​ ​YAAAAYYY!!​ ​​